99centarticles.com 2013-07-26

# 99centarticles.com - Privacy Policy</p>

**99centarticles.com takes your privacy seriously:**   
Our privacy policy is clear and simple: We will collect no personally identifiable information about you when you visit our website or use our services unless you choose to provide that information to us.

**What Does our Privacy Policy Cover?**

This Privacy Policy covers 99centarticles.com's treatment of personally identifiable information that 99centarticles.com collects when you are on the 99centarticles.com site and when you use 99centarticles.com's services. This policy does not describe or cover information collection policies on other sites, including those linked to or from 99centarticles.com.

**No Children under the Age of 13**

99centarticles.com is not directed to children under the age of 13, and children under the age of 13 shall not use the website or services offered by 99centarticles.com to submit any individually identifiable information about themselves.

**What Type of Information Do We Collect?**

99centarticles.com does not collect any personally identifiable information about you other than information that you choose to submit to us, such as your e-mail address, name and address, etc., for example, when you apply to or register as an author or text user on this website or you use or apply to or register for other services on our website.

**How Do We Use the Information?**

The personally identifiable information we collect from and about you may be used to provide e-mail-based newsletters and other information to you and to notify you from time to time about services offered by 99centarticles.com or other entities associated with 99centarticles.com.

**With Whom Will We Share Information?**

We may disclose information about you if we have a good-faith belief that we are required to do so by law or legal process, to respond to claims, or to protect the rights, property or safety of 99centarticles.com, its users, or others. In particular, if a text user brings a claim and/or legal action against the author of a text, we may disclose name, address and other contact information of the author to the text user.

**We Will Delete Personally Identifiable Information We Had Collected About You If You Ask Us To Do So**

You have always the right to demand that we delete personally identifiable information we had collected about you. In this case we will delete all data of or about you from our records / database, unless law or legal process says or demands otherwise (see section 'With Whom Will We Share Information'?).

**What about Updates and Revisions of our Privacy Policy?**

99centarticles.com may revise and update its Privacy Policy at any time without notice by posting such revised or updated Privacy Policy at 

_ www.99centarticles.com/privacy.php_

. Your continued usage of 99centarticles.com or any of its services will mean that you accept these changes.

**Terms of Service**

The 99centarticles.com Terms of Service for customers are available at http://www.99centarticles.com/en/client-tos.php. The 99centarticles.com Terms of Service for authors are available at http://www.99centarticles.com/en/author-tos.php. Please read the Terms of Service Section carefully before using 99centarticles.com.

**Contact us**  
If you have questions or comments about our privacy practices, please feel free to contact us at:  
admin@99centarticles.com.

**Our postal address is:**  
Modern Franchises LLC  
P.O. Box 4672  
Alpharetta, GA 30023
